Guide to the Divinity School Records, circa 1920-2005 UA.19.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files, circa 1920-2005; 156 Linear Feet; 109 boxes
  - Accession A93-129
    - Publicity Materials, 1941 (Box 53)
    - Q - Correspondence, 1930-1937 (Box 53)
    - R - Correspondence, 1928-1941 (Box 53)
    - Reports, 1928-1939 (Box 53)
    - S - Correspondence, 1926-1941 (3 Folders) (Box 53)
    - Statements About Pastors' School, 1934 (Box 53)
    - Student Jobs, 1938-1941 (Box 53)
    - Scholarships, 1935-1941 (Box 53)
    - Sherman, H.H., 1928-1930 (Box 53)
    - T - Correspondence, 1929-1941 (Box 53)
    - V - Correspondence, 1927-1940 (Box 53)
    - W - Correspondence, 1932-1941; 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Papers and Correspondence Re: Pastors' School, 1924-1927; 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Student Grades and Reports (Pastors' School), 1927-1939; 3 folders (Box 53)
    - Statistics of Farmers' Marketing and Purchasing Cooperatives, 1937-1938 Marketing Season, 1939 (Box 54)
    - The Duke Endowment and Rural Church Fund, 1940 (Box 54)
    - Church Painting Data, c.1930s-1940s (Box 54)
    - Dr. R.L. Flowers - Correspondence, 1930-1944 (Box 54)
    - The Duke Fund Commission, c.1920-1940 (Box 54)
    - The Sunday School Magazine - Articles, 1928 (Box 54)
    - Rejected Applications, Summary, 1928 (Box 54)
    - Material Turned Over by Dr. Few, 1920-1926 (Box 54)
    - Duke University Alumni Register, Vol. XV, No. 4, 1929 (Box 54)
    - Reports Re: Rural Churches and Duke Endowment, 1924-1941 (2 Folders) (Box 54)
    - Graham L. Davis - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 54)
    - Wiburt C. Davison - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 54)
    - Duke Endowment Yearbook Reports Re: Rural Church Fund, 1940-1946 (Box 54)
    - J.B. Duke Mission Fund, 1919-1925 (Box 54)
    - Duke Endowment Superannuates, 1915-1949 (Box 54)
    - Committee on Rural Church Reports, 1928-1941 (3 Folders) (Box 54)
    - Student Workshops, 1949 (Box 54)
    - Church Membership by County, c.1925-1950 (Box 54)
    - Rural Life Dept. Ledger, 1930, 1940-1947 (Box 54)
    - J.M. Ormond Fund for Training Rural Ministers, 1948-1949 (Box 54)
    - Papers and Publishings Re: Rural Church Affairs, 1940-1946 (Box 54)
    - Pamphlets Re: Rural Church Affairs, 1942-1946, undated (3 Folders) (Box 54)
    - Department of Negro Work, undated (Box 54)
    - Misc. Papers and Publications, 1940-1946, undated (Box 54)
    - Board of Directors, etc., 1937-1940 (Box 54)
    - A - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 54)
    - B - Correspondence, 1934-1939 (Box 54)
    - Bills, Receipts, etc, 1934-1937 (Box 54)
    - C - Correspondence, 1934-1939 (Box 54)
    - D - Correspondence, 1935-1940 (Box 54)
    - E, F - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 54)
    - Funds Campaign, 1935-1936 (Box 54)
    - Form Letters, 1934-1940 (Box 54)
    - Church Building Fund Apps., 1938-1944 (7 Folders) (Box 54)
    - G - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 54)
    - H, I, J - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 54)
    - K, L - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 54)
    - M - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 55)
    - Minutes - Rural Church Institute, 1934-1940 (Box 55)
    - Misc. Correspondence, 1926-1936 (Box 55)
    - N, O - Correspondence, 1934-1938 (Box 55)
    - P, Q - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 55)
    - R - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 55)
    - S - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 55)
    - Scholarships - Rural Church Institute, 1935-1939 (Box 55)
    - Statements - Rural Church Institute, 1934-1936 (Box 55)
    - T - V - Correspondence, 1935-1940 (Box 55)
    - W - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 55)
    - X - Z, Correspondence, 1931-1936 (Box 55)
  - Accession A83-86
    - Correspondence Re: Scholarship Grants and Funds, 1959-1966 (Box 55)
    - Scholarship Committee, 1966 (Box 55)
    - Awards and Fellowships, Grad. Dept, 1962 (Box 55)
    - Bishop Baker - Graduate Awards Application Form, undated (Box 55)
    - Crusade Scholarships, 1959-1965 (Box 55)
    - Dempster Fellowships, 1960-1965 (Box 55)
    - William Meyers Lauman Scholarship, 1965 (Box 55)
    - Merit Scholarships, 1966 (Box 55)
    - National Methodist Scholarship Reports, 1961 (Box 55)
  - Accession A85-015
    - Papers Re: Thesis Requirements, 1945 (Box 55)
    - Scholarship Funds, 1943-1946 (Box 55)
    - Correspondence Re: WWII and Army/Nay V12 Program, 1943-1946 (Box 55)
    - General Administrative Files and Info About the Divinity School and Library, 1943-1946 (Box 55)
    - WWII - Deferments, 1943-1944 (Box 55)
    - Exams, Courses, Outlines, 1944-1946 (Box 55)
  - Accession A90-63
    - Census Forms, 1974-1980 (3 Folders) (Box 55)
    - General Administrative Files, 1970-1972 (Box 55)
    - Duke Ministerial Course of Study School, 1970-1981 (4 Folders) (Box 55)
    - North Carolina Council of Churches, 1959-1979 (Box 56)
    - The Southern Convention of Congressional Christian Churches, 1959-1960 (Box 56)
    - Brower, A.S., 1950-1957 (Box 56)
    - Dukes, Charles A., 1953-1958 (Box 56)
    - Herring, Herbert J., 1953-1958 (Box 56)
    - Henricksen, G.C., 1951-1960 (Box 56)
    - Howard, W.K., 1954 (Box 56)
    - Jordan, C.E., 1953-1961 (Box 56)
    - Markham, C.B., 1951-1954 (Box 56)
    - Morgan, H.S., 1951-1958 (Box 56)
    - Charles Rice, Charles Foster, John Stapleton, 1973 (Box 56)
    - Methodist Church, Commission to Study the Ministry, 1974 (Box 56)
    - Student Bulletins, 1969-1971 (Box 56)
    - Faculty Bulletins, 1968-1971 (3 Folders) (Box 56)
    - Faculty C.V.'s, 1976 (Box 56)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 56)
    - Divinity School Orientation Program, 1965-1970 (Box 56)
    - Student Association, 1970-1971 (Box 56)
    - Faculty Load, 1969-1970 (Box 56)
    - General Conference, 1975-1977 (2 Folders) (Box 56)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Conference, Atlanta, GA, 1972 (Box 56)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Board of the Ministry Workshop, Lake Junaluska, NC, 1973 (Box 56)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Council, 1958-1977 (Box 56)
    - Jurisdictional Conference, 1972 (Box 56)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Conference, 1976 (Box 56)
    - University Self-Study Memos and Papers, 1972-1977 (3 Folders) (Box 56)
    - United States Methodist Tour Map and North Carolina Map, 1967, 1970 (Box 56)
    - Our Daily Bread and Instructions for Ushers, 1971, 1975 (Box 56)
    - Faculty Bag Lunches, 1975-1977 (Box 56)
    - Alumni News Reported, 1975-1976 (Box 56)
    - Alumni Correspondence, 1976 (Box 56)
    - Alumni Scholarship Fund, 1975-1977 (Box 56)
  - Accession A75-80
    - Duke Circuit Rider, 1952-1957 (Box 57)
  - Accession A90-63
    - Duke Loyalty Fund, 1974-1978 (2 Folders) (Box 58)
    - Faculty Organization, 1978 (Box 58)
    - Alumni Association, 1971-1978 (Box 58)
    - Ph.D. Graduates - Religion, 1975 (Box 58)
    - Alumni Campaign Letter, 1968 (Box 58)
    - Duke Dinner - General Conference, 1972 (Box 58)
    - Roger Marshall - Alumni, 1964-1966 (Box 58)
    - Faculty Publication List, 1970 (Box 58)
    - Faculty Bulletin - Vol. XI - XIII, 1968-1971 (Box 58)
    - Faculty Bulletin Briefs, 1968-1976 (Box 58)
    - Faculty Handbooks, 1972-1973 (Box 58)
    - Faculty Executive Council, 1970 (Box 58)
    - Field Education, 1968-1981 (3 Folders) (Box 58)
    - Financial Aid - General, 1969-1977 (2 Folders) (Box 58)
    - Divinity School Roster, 1969 (Box 58)
    - Minutes of Special Faculty Meeting, 1968 (Box 58)
    - Hart Papers, 1963-1970 (Box 58)
    - Report to the District Conferences of the Methodist Church, 1965-1966 (Box 58)
    - Scholarship Committee, 1968-1975 (Box 58)
    - Interseminary Program, 1972-1973 (Box 58)
    - International Greek New Testament Project (Pres. Ernest Colwell), 1962-1973 (Box 58)
    - South Carolina Conference, 1968 (Box 58)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Fund for Ministerial Education, 1958-1974 (2 Folders) (Box 58)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Fund for Theological Education, 1967-1973 (Box 58)
    - Southeastern Jurisdiction (D. Trigg James), 1968 (Box 58)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Conference, 1964 (Box 58)
    - Southeast Jurisdiction - One Percent Committee, 1965 (Box 58)
    - Student Bulletin, 1969-1971 (Box 58)
    - Student Loans, 1970 (Box 58)
    - Summer Institute, 1973-1974 (2 Folders) (Box 58)
    - Summer Clinics, 1970-1973 (Box 58)
    - Bishops' Advisory Committee, 1976-1977 (2 Folders) (Box 58)
    - Continuing Education, 1976-1978 (Box 58)
    - Committee to Study the Curriculum, 1970-1976 (2 Folders) (Box 59)
    - Duke Endowment General Correspondence, 1965-1979 (Box 59)
    - Faculty Christian Fellowship, 1958 (Box 59)
    - Divinity School Committees, 1974-1975 (Box 59)
    - Special Faculty Meetings, 1963-1966 (Box 59)
    - Moody Smith - Director of Grad. Studies, 1975-1978 (Box 59)
    - International Programs Sub-Committee, 1972 (Box 59)
    - Interpreter's House, 1972-1978 (Box 59)
    - Field Education Seminars, 1974-1977 (Box 59)
    - Junior Seminars, 1969-1970 (Box 59)
    - Lectures Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 59)
    - Program for Info on Variety of Ministers, 1971 (Box 59)
    - M. Div./M.A. Degree Program, 1974-1977 (Box 59)
    - MRE Program, 1968 (Box 59)
    - Middler Honors Program, 1971-1972 (Box 59)
    - Student Petition - Vocational Group V, 1966 (Box 59)
    - Div. School Seminars - V.A. and S.C., 1972 (Box 59)
    - Student Pastor Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 59)
    - Early, Jack J., 1969 (Box 59)
    - Professional Schools Subcommittee, 1972-1973 (Box 59)
    - Rockefeller Theological Fellowships, 1959-1979 (Box 59)
    - Theological Discussion Group, 1972-1976 (Box 59)
    - University Faculty Policies, 1968-1971 (Box 59)
    - University Faculty Meetings, 1969-1972 (Box 59)
    - Dept. of Religion, 1964-1976 (2 Folders) (Box 59)
    - University Planning Committee, 1972 (7 Folders) (Box 59)
    - Search Committee - Chairman, Dept. of Religion, 1971 (Box 59)
    - Pentecost: Church and World, 1972 (Box 59)
    - On This Rock Annual Conferences Sermon, undated (Box 59)
    - Anticipations - Opening Convocation, 1975 (Box 59)
    - Discipline and Discovery - Convocation, 1973 (Box 60)
    - Refinding the Lost Image of Creation: The Holy Spirit and Sanctification, 1973 (Box 60)
    - From Time to Time - Sermon, 1973 (Box 60)
    - Worship Service, 1975 (Box 60)
    - Graduation, 1973 (Box 60)
    - Louisburg Commencement, 1972 (Box 60)
    - Resurrection Experienced, 1973 (Box 60)
    - Borderlands, 1974 (Box 60)
    - The Minister as Scholar - Opening Convocation, 1974 (Box 60)
    - Davidson College Commencement, 1975 (Box 60)
    - Palm Sunday, 1975 (Box 60)
    - The Last Supper and Christian Discipleship, 1976 (Box 60)
    - The Context of Theological Education, 1976 (Box 60)
    - Faculty Seminar, 1976 (Box 60)
    - Penance and Words of Assurance, 1977 (Box 60)
    - Sermon by Thomas A. Langford, 1972 (Box 60)
    - Celebration and Concern, 1976 (Box 60)
    - Torrance Festschrift, 1975-1977 (Box 60)
    - Opening Address - Union Seminary, Richmond, VA, 1978 (Box 60)
    - Theological Assessment of Theological Education, 1978 (Box 60)
    - Chaplain's Seminar - A Theology for Tomorrow, 1972 (Box 60)
    - Willson Lectures - Wesley Theological Seminary, 1974 (Box 60)
    - On Being World Christians, undated (Box 60)
    - Thomas A. Langford - Misc. Addresses, Prayers, and Sermons, 1963-1977, undated (2 Folders) (Box 60)
    - ATS - Atlanta, GA, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
    - American Association of Theological Schools, 1972-1978 (2 Folders) (Box 60)
    - ATS Program Committee - Toronto, Ontario, 1977 (Box 60)
    - ATS Meeting Materials, 1978 (Box 60)
    - ATS Executive Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 60)
    - ATS Meeting, Toronoto, 1978 (Box 60)
    - Association of United Methodist Schools - Colorado Springs, 1978 (Box 60)
    - AUMTS Consortium on Internationalization of Theological Education, 1978 (Box 60)
    - AUMTS Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1978 (2 Folders) (Box 60)
    - AUMTS - Milwaukee, WI, 1977 (Box 60)
    - AUMTS - Atlanta, GA, 1976 (Box 60)
    - AUMTS - Misc., 1972-1979 (Box 60)
    - AUMTS - Albuquerque, NM, 1979 (Box 60)
    - AUMTS - Boston, MA, 1979 (Box 60)
    - AUMTS - Chicago, Il, 1979 (Box 60)
    - AUMTS - Williamsburg, VA, 1977-1978 (Box 60)
    - AUMTS - Atlanta, GA, 1974 (Box 60)
    - AATS Summer Workshop Seminar, 1971 (Box 60)
    - The United Methodist Reporter, 1971 (Box 60)
    - Board of Higher Education and Ministry, 1976 (Box 60)
    - Bailey, Lloyd, 1971-1982 (Box 61)
    - Cushman, Robert E., 1970-1981 (Box 61)
    - Efrid, James M., 1964-1982 (2 Folders) (Box 61)
    - Elsinger, Richard, 1983-1987 (Box 61)
    - Farris, Donn M., 1962-1982 (2 Folders) (Box 61)
    - Gilbert, Paula, 1978-1983 (Box 61)
    - Goodling, Richard A., 1963-1986 (2 Folders) (Box 61)
    - Goodson, Bishop W. Kenneth, 1962-1982 (Box 61)
    - Gregg, Robert C., 1974-1984 (Box 61)
    - Herzog, Frederick, 1961-1982 (3 Folders) (Box 61)
    - Henry, Stuart C., 1964-1982 (2 Folders) (Box 61)
    - Lacy, Creighton, 1962-1982 (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - Langford, Thomas A., 1980-1982 (Box 61)
    - Lischer, Richard, 1974-1983 (Box 61)
    - Mickey, Paul A., 1970-1983 (2 Folders) (Box 61)
  - Accession A90-68
    - St. Michael's Parish, Dumfries, Scotland, 1956-1980 (7 Folders) (Box 62)
    - Scotland (Non-Dumfries), 1969-1974 (Box 62)
    - United Methodist Theological Schools Recruitment Officers, 1969, 1972 (Box 62)
    - C.M. 9, Section III, 1972 (Box 62)
    - Dept. of Ministerial Education, 1958-1966 (Box 62)
    - General Board of Lay Activities, 1962 (Box 62)
    - Deaconess News and Views, 1964 (Box 62)
    - World Methodist Council, 1961-1965 (Box 62)
    - The National Association of Schools and Colleges of the Methodist Church, 1959-1968 (Box 62)
    - Town and Country Commission, 1960-1962 (Box 62)
    - Television, Radio and Film Commission (TRAFCO), 1965 (Box 62)
    - District Lay Rally, 1972 (Box 62)
    - Appalachian Area Study Conference, 1962 (Box 62)
    - Board of Methodist Church - Division of World Missions, 1962-1966 (Box 62)
    - Commission on World Service and Finance, 1963-1966 (Box 62)
    - Christian Social Concerns, 1961-1966 (Box 62)
    - Judicial Council - Methodist Church, 1962-1964 (Box 62)
    - Methodist Theological Schools Enrollment, 1969-1970 (Box 62)
    - National Association of Schools and Colleges, Cinicinnati, Ohio, 1971 (Box 62)
    - AMTS - Council of Bishops, 1965 (Box 62)
    - President's Bulletin Board, 1964-1971 (Box 62)
    - Rouch, Mark A., 1964-1969 (Box 62)
    - Seminary Financial Aid Resources Inventory, 1965 (Box 62)
    - Wickey, Dr. Myron F., 1964-1969 (Box 62)
    - AUMTS Meeting - Des Moines, Iowa, 1971 (Box 62)
    - Likins, William H., 1969-1974 (2 Folders) (Box 62)
    - Dept. of Ministerial Education, Board of Education of the Methodist Church, 1961-1972 (Box 62)
    - Oxford Edition of Wesley's Works, Bulletin No. 7, undated (Box 62)
    - Duke United Ministry, 1971 (Box 62)
    - Association of Methodist Theological Schools - Minutes, 1938-1958 (Box 62)
    - Rural Church Affairs, 1974 (Box 62)
  - Accession A90-78
    - Bishops' Advisory Committee, 1959-1976 (5 Folders) (Box 63)
    - Church Architecture (Conference Committees), 1971-1976 (Box 63)
    - Rural Church Committee, 1962-1975 (Box 63)
    - Rural Church Committee Reports, 1960-1968 (Box 63)
    - Powell, Mrs. Mattie Bell, 1959-1968 (Box 63)
    - N.C. U.M. Commission on Continuing Education for Ministers, 1972 (Box 63)
    - Nesbitt, M. Wilson, 1960-1974 (2 Folders) (Box 63)
    - Rural Lay Meeting, 1972 (Box 63)
    - Duke Endowment Meeting, 1973 (Box 63)
    - Executive Council - Business Grad. Division of Religion, 1963-1975 (Box 63)
    - Graduate Division Minutes, 1960-1975 (Box 63)
    - Th. M. Program, 1960-1970 (Box 63)
    - Rockefeller Doctoral Program, 1969 (Box 63)
    - Division of Grad Students, 1969-1975 (Box 63)
    - Graduate Studies Affairs, 1963-1974 (3 Folders) (Box 63)
    - Young, Frank - Director of Graduate Program, 1969-1973 (Box 63)
    - Divinity School Committees, 1971-1973 (Box 63)
    - Committee Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 63)
    - Admissions Committee Business, 1968-1969 (Box 63)
    - Chapel Worship Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 63)
    - Curriculum Subcommittee, 1970 (Box 63)
    - Financial Aid Committee, 1971 (Box 63)
    - Scholarship Committee, 1969 (Box 63)
    - Divinity School Committees, 1963-1971 (Box 63)
    - Admissions and Related, 1970 (Box 63)
    - Admissions Reports, 1971 (Box 63)
    - Advisor-Advisee, 1959-1970 (Box 63)
    - Black Recruitment, 1970-1971 (Box 63)
    - Black Church Studies, 1970-1974 (3 Folders) (Box 63)
    - Black Seminarians Union, 1970-1975 (Box 63)
  - Accession A94-1
    - Board of Ministry, WNC Conference, 1972-1976 (2 Folders) (Box 64)
    - Western NC Conference, 1973 (Box 64)
    - Institute for Homitletical Studies - WNC Conference (Box 64)
    - General Conference, 1972-1975 (Box 64)
    - WNC Board of the Ministry, Elk Shoals, NC, 1974 (Box 64)
    - WNC Board of the Ministry, Charlotte, NC, 1973 (Box 64)
    - AATS and AUMTS - St. Paul, Minnesota, 1972 (Box 64)
    - World Service Bulletin, 1958-1971 (Box 64)
    - Ministry Newsletter, 1971 (Box 64)
    - The Higher Education Planning and Strategy Committee, 1969-1975 (2 Folders) (Box 64)
    - AUMTS Meeting - Nashville, TN., 1972-1973 (Box 64)
    - United Methodist Church Misc., 1971-1976 (2 Folders) (Box 64)
    - Commision on Chaplains - Methodist Church, 1958-1973 (Box 64)
    - Discussion on Ministerial Education, Kansas City, MO, 1973 (Box 64)
    - Board of Education - Harold Porter, 1972-1975 (Box 64)
    - Commission to Study the Ministry of the Church, 1973-1974 (Box 64)
    - Meeting - Methodist Related University Presidents, 1972 (Box 64)
    - AUMTS - Nasheville, TN, 1972-1975 (Box 64)
    - AUMTS - Atlanta, GA, 1974 (Box 64)
    - Hinton Rural Life Center - The United Methodist Church, 1969 (Box 64)
    - Consultation on Campus Ministry, 1976 (Box 64)
    - AUMTS - Chicago, Il, 1975 (Box 64)
    - AUMTS - Kansas City, MO, 1976 (Box 64)
    - Consultation Task Force - Wesley Theological Seminary, 1973-1975 (2 Folders) (Box 64)
    - Commission to Study the Ministry, 1973-1976 (Box 64)
    - Higher Education Planning and Strategy Committee, Quail Roost, 1973 (Box 64)
    - Bishops' Conference on United Methodist Higher Education in North Carolina - Greensboro, NC, 1972-1975 (Box 64)
    - Joint Hiigher Education Planning and Strategy Committee NC and WNC Annual Conferences, 1974 (Box 64)
  - Accession A2005-0016
    - Installation - L. Gregory Jones, Dean, 1997 (Box 65)
    - Congratulatory Letters - Installation of Dean L. Gregory Jones, 1997 (2 Folders) (Box 65)
    - Photographs Featuring Terry Sanford, Jameson James, and others, undated (Box 65)
    - Campaign for Duke, 1998 (Box 65)
    - Self-Study of the Divinity School, 1983-1984 (Box 65)
    - Report of the Self-Study, 1983 (Box 65)
    - Report of the Self-Study, 1993 (Box 65)
    - Association for Christian Training and Service, 1997-1998 (Box 65)
    - ACTS Meeting - Duke Divinity School, 1997 (Box 65)
    - ACTS Meeting - Durham, NC, 1996 (Box 65)
    - Secretariat of Ecumenical and Interreligious Affairs, 1997 (Box 65)
    - General Commission on Christian Unity and International Concerns, 1993-1998 (Box 65)
    - Bonn Exchange Program, 1981-2002 (Box 65)
    - Bonn Group Meeting, Durham, NC, 1997 (Box 65)
    - Bonn Group Leaves for Germany, 1996 (Box 65)
    - Duke-Bonn Dinner, 2003 (Box 65)
    - Duke Divinity School Addition, 2000 (Box 65)
    - Bonn, 1983 (Box 65)
    - Divinity School - Landscape Master Plan, 1993 (Box 65)
    - Divinity School - Space Needs Assessment, 1990 (Box 65)
  - Accession A75-80
    - Hannavee, 1969-1983, undated (4 Folders) (Box 65)
    - Listening, 1976-1984 (4 Folders) (Box 65)
    - Duke Divinity School in Ministry, 1975-1983 (Box 65)
    - Response, 1957-1975 (13 Folders) (Box 66)
    - Christian Edukeation, 1986-1988 (Box 66)
    - Christian Horizons, 1949 (Box 66)
    - The Divinity Enquirer, 1982-1983 (Box 66)
    - Ahead of the Times, 1992 (Box 66)
    - The Divinity School Worship Book, 1971 (Box 66)
    - Centerpiece (Center for Continuing Education), 1990-1991 (Box 66)
    - The Preceptor, 1997 (Box 66)
    - Misc. Publications, 1974-1989 (Box 66)
    - The Sojourner, 1975-1996 (Box 66)
    - Sisters Letters, 1974 (Box 66)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1989-1999 (Box 66)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted until 2024.
  - Accession 92-67
    - Press Clippings, 1988-1991 (4 Folders) (Box 67)
  - Accession A94-1
    Administrative records are restricted for 25 years from their date of origin, however published materials are not subject to this restriction. Please contact Research Services for more information.
    - Boston University School of Theology, Self-Appraisal Balance Sheet for the Eastern Seabord Regional Task Force, 1974 (Box 67)
    - The United Methodist Theological Schools in the Eastern Seabord Region, 1973 (Box 67)
    - Higher Education Planning and Strategy Committee - Quail Roost, 1974 (Box 67)
    - Rationale for Church Support of Higher Education, 1973-1975 (Box 67)
    - Joint Committee on Higher Education, 1974 (Box 67)
    - Faculty Data for News and Notes, 1991-1994 (Box 67)
    - Advertising Contracts, 1974 (Box 67)
    - Budget: Requests, Current Records, and Expenditures, 1976-1980 (Box 67)
    - Christian Horizons, 1940-1941 (Box 67)
    - Copyright Certificates, 1977-1980 (Box 67)
    - Divinity School Annual - Correspondence, 1951-1983 (Box 67)
    - Permission Letters - Reprints, 1974 (Box 67)
    - Printing: Contracts, Estimates, 1972-1974 (Box 67)
    - Response, 1962-1976 (Box 67)
    - Student Publications, 1977-1981 (Box 67)
    - Subscriptions, 1977-1978 (Box 67)
    - The Between Times, 1984-1985 (Box 67)
  - Accession A97-11
    - American Academy of Religion, 1979-1988 (Box 67)
    - Andean Rural Health Project, 1981-1985 (Box 67)
    - Appalachian Ministries Educational Resource Center, 1985-1986 (Box 67)
    - Appeal of Conscience Foundation, 1983-1986 (Box 67)
    - Bach Festival, 1983-1985 (Box 67)
    - Bailey, Mrs. Dorothy B., 1925-1985 (Box 67)
    - Bishop's Seminar on Ministry, 1984 (Box 67)
    - Branscomb, Harvie, 1944-1985 (Box 67)
    - White v. Bressler Trial, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Candidacy Program, 1981-1983 (Box 67)
    - Cathey, Robert A., 1985-1986 (Box 67)
    - Chavis, Ben, 1978-1979 (Box 67)
    - Cheezem, Paul, 1984 (Box 67)
    - China Scholars, 1984-1986 (Box 67)
    - Commission on Religion in Appalachia, 1984-195 (Box 67)
    - Staley Lectures, Columbia College, 1984-1985 (Box 67)
    - Correspondence Re: Comm./Pub. Relations Position, 1983 (Box 67)
    - Consulting Firms, 1987 (Box 67)
    - Craven, Jim, 1984-1985 (Box 67)
    - St. Michael's Parish, Dumfries, Scotland, 1980-1986 (Box 67)
    - Dunston, Earl M., 1984 (Box 67)
    - Elliott, Melzie E., 1978-1985 (Box 67)
    - Ellis, Steve, 1981-1982 (Box 67)
    - Dedication - Engineering Library, 1984 (Box 67)
    - Hayes, Don, undated (Box 67)
    - Hilton Inn, Durham, NC, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Iona Community, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Lewis, Douglas, 1983-1985 (Box 67)
    - Lincoln, Dr. Eric, 1980-1982 (Box 67)
    - Lind, Mrs. Theodore, 1976-1977 (Box 67)
    - Luce, Henry R., Professorship, 1977-1979 (Box 68)
    - St. Margaret's-McTernan School, 1982-1983 (Box 68)
    - North Charles Street Design, 1985 (Box 68)
    - Parish Ministries Fund Meeting - Charlotte, NC, 1987-1989 (Box 68)
    - Parish Ministries Fund Meeting - Spindale, NC, 1986-1988 (Box 68)
    - Parish Ministries Fund Meetings, 1984-1990 (Box 68)
    - Parish Ministry Fund Financial Reports, 1977-1991 (Box 68)
    - Parish Ministry Fund - General, 1977-1991 (2 Folders) (Box 68)
    - Perkins School of Theology - Southern Meth. U., 1988-1989 (3 Folders) (Box 68)
    - Blue Ribbon Task Force - Perkins School, 1989 (Box 68)